程序可以运行对于一个程序猿来说是最开心的了。下面，我将展示
I know you're excited to run the app. And I'm going to show you how to do it
在没有物理设备的情况下，我们还能用模拟器来运行程序。
without a physical device, because we'll be using the emulator.
首先，我们需要在Android SDK 中多安装一个组件。
But first, we need to install one more component from the Android SDK Manager.
单击，打开 Android SDK 管理器。
Click on this button to open up the Android SDK Manager.
找到列表底部的HAXM。这是硬件加速执行管理器。
Scroll to the bottom ofthe list to find HAXM. It stands for hardware accelerated execution manager.
它能给模拟器加速。取消其他的安装选项，我们只安装HAXM。
And it will speed up our emulator. So go ahead and deselect the other packages, and
接受许可，继续。
just install this one. Accept the license, and then continue.
在安装前我们还需要一些步骤。
We have to do one more step after this to install HAXM.
这里将介绍Mac上的安装步骤，而其他平台上的操作请从下方的链接处学习。
I'll show you the remaining steps on a Mac, but for the other platforms you can
首先，找到 Android Studio 下的应用程序文件夹，
check the link below. First, find Android Studio under the applications folder,
打开 show package contents。在SDK文件夹下，
and then hit show package contents. Then, in the SDK folder,
包含一个extras文件夹，这个文件夹下的Intel文件夹里包含了HAXM运行程序。
there'll be an extras folder containing an Intel folder with the HAXM folder.
运行这个DMG文件，点击继续。
Then, we click on the DMG file, open it up and then continue.
通过这个步骤安装，默认是是ok的。
Step through this installer, and the default values are fine.
安装完成后，就可以关闭所有的窗口。O(∩_∩)O哈哈~
Once installation is complete, you can close all the windows.